<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-06-26T02:41:52+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sciloo Learning Technologies</title><subtitle>Sciloo Learning Technologies</subtitle><entry><title type="html">I want to start selling T-shirts. Where do I begin?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/I-want-to-start-selling-T-shirts-Where-do-I-begin" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I want to start selling T-shirts. Where do I begin?" /><published>2021-06-21T23:26:25+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-21T23:26:25+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/I-want-to-start-selling-T-shirts-Where-do-I-begin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/I-want-to-start-selling-T-shirts-Where-do-I-begin">&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-want-to-start-selling-t-shirts-where-do-i-begin&quot;&gt;I want to start selling T-shirts. Where do I begin?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will recommend you to you start a business where less competition is present and you have the pricing power. You need to be clear why you want to start specifically Tshirt business. There is a huge competition in clothing, you will really need to think about scaling your business and margins. 
If you still want to start it. First remember start small. Have some design for the target audience (select gender age etc.). You should be clear who is your user/consumer. Then contact manufacturers who can make your design (fabric types/quality, gsm, print). They can ask you for huge minimum quantity for the order but initially verify your business don’t go for margins but plan to be profitable. You need to think where you will store and how you will ship. We do it via amazon. you can search sciloo on 
https://amzn.to/3ntpUwF&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;key points&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;start small&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;test your idea (may be if you can get 5–10 samples, quickly try to sell online)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;build brand by satisfying customers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;sell the vision not cloth (customer should associate to your idea)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="startup" /><category term="startup" /><summary type="html">I want to start selling T-shirts. Where do I begin?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What to look for when buying any Product</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Buying-any-Product-What-to-look-for" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What to look for when buying any Product" /><published>2021-06-20T23:50:15+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-20T23:50:15+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Buying%20any%20Product%20What%20to%20look%20for</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Buying-any-Product-What-to-look-for">&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
When we buy a product, mostly we first focus on
	use, 
	then price
	then brand
	mostly forget safety
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People focus mostly on the price and use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3xzh6s-a8F8&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You get a product that may work
but will it work as desired over a long period of time safely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if you have focussed on money not the quality then the product can be risky and the money you used to buy it can become wasted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should have focussed about the use, safety, brand and price.
why brand is more imp than price
	we need to understand what is a brand first.
		brand is a company name or name of a product range which get	
		famous because
			it is made with high quality materials
			made with established processes
			has safety of the customers in mind 
			has been tested in different conditions over a long period of time
				it gives it reliablity and safety.
			They give warranty which can be relied upon in real life.
		local brands may not have these because they are just selling products not disclosing the processes, not disclosing whether they actually made or designed the product or just relabel a chinese or local made item with their logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I give you a example
	If you want to buy a good headphone
		will you buy a local headphone if you your use is very high quality music with comfort
		or you will go with bose.
			You should go with bose, reason is they have mastered the sound and comfort for the listener.
		same for a mixer grinder will you buy a philips one or a local one.
			I recommend philips because they are leaders in the field and do good amount of research on each product they make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I request you to provide your experiences in buying a branded or unbranded product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t recommed you to buy new products as you should save money, invest money for your financial independence.
You should buy used products but don’t buy used electronics and high value products from unknowns or without written quarantees because trust is missing.
Anything that you can inspect and validate you can buy used.
&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="Awareness" /><category term="Help" /><category term="General" /><category term="Advice" /><summary type="html">When we buy a product, mostly we first focus on use, then price then brand mostly forget safety People focus mostly on the price and use.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Experiment – Generation Of Electricity from Wind</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/03/31/experiment-generation-of-electricity-from-wind/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Experiment – Generation Of Electricity from Wind" /><published>2019-03-31T23:50:15+05:30</published><updated>2019-03-31T23:50:15+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/03/31/experiment-generation-of-electricity-from-wind</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/03/31/experiment-generation-of-electricity-from-wind/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Wind is moving air and caused by differences in air pressure within our atmosphere or we can say it is the flow of gases on a large scale. Wind is caused by uneven heating of the atmosphere by the sun, variations in the earth’s surface, and rotation of the earth. Mountains, bodies of water, and vegetation all influence wind flow patterns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Wind is also used to generate electricity. For the generation of electricity from wind, we use wind turbines. A wind turbine works the opposite of a fan. Instead of using electricity to make wind, like a fan, wind turbines use wind to make electricity. The wind turns the blades which connect to a generator and makes electricity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiment in Lab:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We performed this experiment in our Lab. For wind energy generator experiment we need one dc motor, one LED, one turbine which we rotate with fan or wind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Procedure:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Make a turbine with either a plastic bottle or with cardboard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Untitled.png&quot; alt=&quot;This image has an empty alt attribute; its file name is Untitled.png&quot; width=&quot;164&quot; height=&quot;175&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stick the turbine to a stand. Fix the stand on dc motor with both of motor input current points are connected to the LED.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; class=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Untitled1.png&quot; alt=&quot;This image has an empty alt attribute; its file name is Untitled1.png&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;167&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Now, place the turbine in front of the electric fan. As the motor blade rotates, it rotates the shaft of the motor which generates electricity and the LED glows. We will post the video of the experiment soon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, we are converting one form on energy to another (wind to electricity). The magnet inside the motor rotates which induces the current in the motor winding using induction and this induced current give electricity to the connected led.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="Education" /><category term="YoungScienceLab" /><category term="experiment" /><category term="physics" /><summary type="html">Wind is moving air and caused by differences in air pressure within our atmosphere or we can say it is the flow of gases on a large scale. Wind is caused by uneven heating of the atmosphere by the sun, variations in the earth’s surface, and rotation of the earth. Mountains, bodies of water, and vegetation all influence wind flow patterns.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Observation Research and Study</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/03/05/observation-research-and-study/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Observation Research and Study" /><published>2019-03-05T22:45:20+05:30</published><updated>2019-03-05T22:45:20+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/03/05/observation-research-and-study</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/03/05/observation-research-and-study/">&lt;table class=&quot;wp-block-table&quot;&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      Subject
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;1.&amp;nbsp; Problem/Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      Increase satisfaction and ease of use when interacting with a refrigerator. Basically, we need to improve the design and functionalities of the refrigerator to make it more user-friendly, easy to use and feature rich to satisfy our customers. To achieve this goal, we have to hear what our customers and stakeholders are looking for in a good solution.
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;2.&amp;nbsp; References&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.elsevier.com/wps/find/journaldescription.cws_home/30436/description#description&quot;&gt;International Journal of Refrigeration&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;1.%09http:/www.chemistry.wustl.edu/~courses/genchem/LabTutorials/Thermochem/Fridge.html&quot;&gt;Principles of refrigeration working Washington University at St Louis&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://panasonic.com/industrial/includes/pdf/invertercompressors-improvingefficiency.pdf&quot;&gt;http://panasonic.com/industrial/includes/pdf/invertercompressors-improvingefficiency.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://freeonlinesurveys.com/rendersurvey.asp?sid=so68kif9b3jo0ad958434&quot;&gt;http://freeonlinesurveys.com/rendersurvey.asp?sid=so68kif9b3jo0ad958434&lt;/a&gt; &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;3.&amp;nbsp; Assumptions&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      Surveys conducted are anonymous, only type of user (home, working, etc.) is askedOur scope is limited to the interaction with the refrigerator; very less or no consideration is given to the environment in which refrigerator is being used.Survey and Interview sample size is 20-25 peoples having different level of interactions and use cases with the refrigerator. We assumed this sample size is enough for our scope.We are assuming that we are doing all these exercises to improve a business position in the market. &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;4.&amp;nbsp; Results&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      The main pain areas resulting from user interviews, contextual observations, surveys &amp;nbsp;with the refrigerator use are: The refrigerator is not modular and doesn’t suit the containers if they are very large or small.Very painful to every time open the door just to see what is there inside and control the temperature.Very difficult to move from one place to other to clean it or floor under it.Almost all the participants wanted some indication in a display like temperature, capacity, odor level etc. The other interesting finding is that customers like their brands with their heart and would not like to switch to different brand if purchasing a new refrigerator but can reconsider their decision if reliability in the form of warranty is provided.
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;5.&amp;nbsp; Conclusions&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      The main findings are that user (voice of almost all users) wants to save the time while interacting with and using the refrigerator. He wants nearly everything to be automated, handy, and easy to use with low learning curve. We have suggested few design changes and inclusion of new technologies like electronic nose to detect odor in the refrigerator and alarming, use of LEDs for saving power and providing uniform lighting, inverter technology of using the compressor heat to efficiently convert back to electric power and demand based power usage. Proposed Recommendations: Provision of giving settings controls and LCD/LED display outside the refrigerator so the user needs not to open the door and bend every time just to check or change the temperature, see inside the refrigerator.Transparent Walls with reversible opaque capability. Person with the press of switch or remote can switch between transparent exterior and opaque exterior.Modular design &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;1-problem-statement&quot;&gt;&lt;a&gt;1.    Problem Statement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Increase satisfaction and ease of use when interacting with a refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objectives are to observe, interact with the users and prospective buyers to know their needs and understand their feelings when they use a refrigerator. Basically, what they see as limitations in their usage and what things they desire when buying a new refrigerator will be good opportunities to increase the ease of use and satisfy users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;2-results-and-analysis&quot;&gt;&lt;a&gt;2.    Results and Analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To lead in the competition you need to hear and understand the voice of customers, potential buyers, and all the stakeholders and adapting the product/business strategies accordingly. The current problem belongs to the refrigerator market segment and the problem is how we can satisfy variety of users by delivering better quality and feature rich refrigerator meeting their needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For solving this problem, we needed to collect, process the data of how different types of users use a refrigerator and what features they see in a refrigerator that they will surely buy if one such refrigerator comes to the market. We will discuss below how we came to the same frame and thinking level in which the users were thinking and what recommendations we proposed to achieve the desired problem objective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will walk you through the process that we followed from connecting with the users, getting their needs to build the solutions. Overview of the process is given below; detailed steps will be explained in sufficient depth in this section after the overview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Understanding the problem and its background&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planning the journey ahead&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Goal settings for user observations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strategy for interviews&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pre observation data and questionnaire&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Observation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Debriefing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data analysis and categorization&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finding improvement areas and recommendations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ideation, evaluation, and prototyping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s discuss these process steps one by one in context of how we performed them and what artifacts we collected and analyzed at every step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;21-understanding-problem-and-its-background&quot;&gt;2.1    Understanding problem and its background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this exercise was to understand the problem and its context. We have discussed this part in the start of Section 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;22-planning-the-journey-ahead&quot;&gt;2.2    Planning the journey ahead&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We planned what exactly we need to do next and what different steps we have to follow to reach till the solutions. We discussed in the team that we need to interact with the users in best possible ways. To achieve this objective we defined our goals and scope under which we will be interacting with the end users and the stake holders. We planned to do the team work till the data consolidations and after that solutions/prototypes will be done individually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This planning resulted in steps from 2.3 to 2.10 below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;23-goal-settings-for-user-observations&quot;&gt;2.3    Goal settings for user observations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We defined the goals and scope of our tasks which will guide and keep us on track in the data collection process and user observations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below are the goals we brainstormed and scoped as our boundary:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;231-usage-type-of-refrigerator&quot;&gt;2.3.1   Usage type of Refrigerator&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example: making ice, water cooling, protecting perishable food items, storing milk, meat, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;232-functionality-improvements&quot;&gt;2.3.2   Functionality improvements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example: faster cooling, uniform temperature at around all the corners, odor detection and control, capacity indicator, rotten item indicator, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;233-design-improvements&quot;&gt;2.3.3   Design improvements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example: exteriors and interiors, mobility, accessing door, modular design, noiseless operation etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;234-reduced-energy-consumption&quot;&gt;2.3.4   Reduced energy consumption&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;235-understanding-types-of-users-age-sex-culture-and-location-wise-etc&quot;&gt;2.3.5   Understanding types of users (Age, Sex, Culture, and location wise, etc.)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;24-strategy-for-observation&quot;&gt;2.4    Strategy for observation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We used the following user observation methods explained with the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;241-user-interviews&quot;&gt;2.4.1   User Interviews&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can be done in person or over the phone. It is one of the best techniques because you directly interact with a user and can interject questions in a dynamic environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;242-participatory-observation-with-context&quot;&gt;2.4.2   Participatory observation with context&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To understand things from the point of view of users and        making them feel comfortable that we are there to help them and solve their problems. You can see them using or working with the refrigerators and observe their particular way of doing some things and can interject your questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;243-surveys&quot;&gt;2.4.3   Surveys&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook polls for getting problems from variety of the users. We received ~10 survey results by using this method. (Refer Point 4 in Section 2 of Design Study Summary).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;244-video&quot;&gt;2.4.4   Video&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You get the feel of behavior/dynamic flow of refrigerator and usage workflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;245-photos&quot;&gt;2.4.5   Photos&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can point to a particular problem or improvement area. Photos are also useful to give the feel of environment and layout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;246-focus-group&quot;&gt;2.4.6   Focus group&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To collect the pre observation data with some interacting group. We three participant did the discussion among ourselves on initial set of questions and basic understanding of the context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;25-pre-observation-data-and-questionnaire&quot;&gt;2.5    Pre observation data and questionnaire&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this step, we identified key contact persons who we will be contacting for the observation and did some pre research about our users to prepare some personas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; We also planned and estimated the time duration during which we will be contacting them or observing them and scheduled prior meetings with them. Also, based on our goals we brainstormed some questions to be put in questionnaire. Goal wise questions are provided below (for goals refer to section 2.3):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;251-usagefunctionality-types-of-a-refrigerator&quot;&gt;2.5.1   Usage/Functionality types of a refrigerator.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q1: What are your different uses of a refrigerator like ice making, water cooling etc.?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q2. Can you briefly tell us your one day cycle of interaction with the refrigerator from Morning till sleep?                 You can only describe the things related to the use of refrigerator, no personal data is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q3. Do you see any limitation in its usage like speed of cooling, hard to use and cleaning?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q4. Do you want to suggest new improvement or idea that can make refrigerator easy to use for you       or other people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q5. Are you content with temperature control or will you like to see some changes in the mechanism?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q6. Do you like the food placed in the refrigerator to eat?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q7. Have you faced any problem or limitation when you were demanding something from the refrigerator and it was not able to deliver?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q8. Have you seen such problems with other peoples?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q9. Do you want to have some kind of signals for refrigerator like when it is opened, tone will alert you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q.10 Have you faced any problem related to odor or fungus in your refrigerator?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;252-design-improvements&quot;&gt;2.5.2   Design improvements&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q1. Do you like the design of your refrigerator?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q2. What do you like in your refrigerator design?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q3. What changes you want to see in the exteriors and interiors of the refrigerator to improve it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q4. Any limitation you felt by the design?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q5. Do you need to move your refrigerator from one place to another, if yes, can you move it easily?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q6. Are you able to fit the containers you have in this refrigerator or you needing more space?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q7. Do you think that we should manufacture refrigerator with green technology?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q8. Are you aware about the design/different parts of your refrigerator?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;253-reduced-energy-consumption&quot;&gt;2.5.3   Reduced energy consumption&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q1. Do you think that you refrigerator is energy efficient?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q2. It is related to Q1. If not, why you think so?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q3. Do you have any idea in how we can make it more efficient?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;254-understanding-type-of-users&quot;&gt;2.5.4   Understanding type of users&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q1. Get filled the user profile survey sheet from users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q2. Did you face any danger possibility when children are near refrigerator?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Q3. Do you need extra warranty at some extra nominal cost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q4. Do you have emotional attachment with your refrigerator, if yes then why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;26-observation&quot;&gt;2.6    Observation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this period, we observed and interacted with the users based on our goals, questionnaire, and assumptions. We followed the observation methods (see section 2.4) as agreed upon. We got the surveys filled, had interviews with the users, took photo/video shoots of usage and environment for the data. We planned to meet after the data collection at a pre-determined time and place. The user problems and stories are given in Appendix B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;27-debriefing&quot;&gt;2.7    Debriefing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we collected the data, we assembled at the place of meeting and briefed each of us about the tasks each of us performed. We wrote everything on the paper notes and pasted them on the board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also captured the users observed for later consolidation along with “Let Go” solution provided by the users or us during the observation period. “Let Go” solutions are basically the solution that comes to your mind intuitively on the spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We followed three steps process for the debriefing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;271-debriefing-on-the-board&quot;&gt;2.7.1   Debriefing on the board&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each person will explain what he has collected and put it on the board in the proper identifiable and readable manner.&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1131&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 1 – Debrief Session after observation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;272-brainstorming-and-data-consolidation-on-the-board&quot;&gt;2.7.2   Brainstorming and data consolidation on the board&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we as a group went to the board to find the similar improvement areas and user roles and consolidated them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1132&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 2 – Brainstorming &amp;amp; Prioritization of stories and collected data&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;273-prioritization-of-the-consolidated-on-the-board&quot;&gt;2.7.3   Prioritization of the consolidated on the board&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everybody assigned priorities to the consolidated items along with few key users. We did the work of note taking, moderation and work modeling in this step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1133&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 3 – Consolidated &amp;amp; prioritized data&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;28-data-analysis-and-categorization&quot;&gt;2.8    Data analysis and categorization&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the debrief session and brainstorming, we formed the categories of the problem areas or improvements area. We also consolidated user roles (refer to Appendix A) and prepared user profiles (Refer Table 1).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Table 1 – User Profiles&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1134&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;29-finding-improvement-areas-and-recommendations&quot;&gt;2.9    Finding improvement areas and recommendations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before going for the recommendation for the problems or key finding, let’s us have some actual refrigerator photos where the problems are reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compressor and circuits are exposed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 4 clearly shows that compressor and wires are exposed outside. Compressor is very hot, and exposed wires if cut can increase the danger of electrocution. We will need to solve this problem for safety point of view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some shield could have provided on the back side of the refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-4.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1135&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 4 – Exposed wires and Compressor and unknown things (No labeling)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time consuming mechanical things like locks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see in the Figure 5 below lock is provided to safeguard against small kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lock is a simple mechanical lock with keys, and consumes time to lock and finding keys. This could have been a button to toggle lock and unlock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-5.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1136&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 5 – Mechanical Lock and Non transparent door&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No proper labeling/help&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 6 clearly shows a violation in proper labeling of the circuits and components of a refrigerator. This component pointed in the figure can be a dangerous thing if unknowingly touched or overlooked (Well, I don’t know, no label is there).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-6.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1137&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 6 – No Labeling, awaiting possible hazard&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobility problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 7 shows an example of the mobility problem when the refrigerator is placed in the corner and we can’t open its door fully to pull out a container outside or when somebody wants to clean the refrigerator inside. This mobility limitation comes in the way again when you want to displace the refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-7.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1138&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 7 – No wheels for mobility and Refrigerator environment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We used the conjoint analysis for the evaluating the recommendations. Check the result section of Design Study Summary or Discussion section 3.5 for the recommendation we proposed. For detailed recommendation, please refer to Appendix D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;210-ideation-evaluation-and-prototyping&quot;&gt;2.10    Ideation, evaluation, and prototyping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end, we brainstormed and discussed among ourselves and with the users to propose solutions in terms of mock ups or prototypes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the promising recommendations are given in section 3.6 for which mock ups and sketches are made. For all the recommendations you can refer to Appendix D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;211-nomenclature&quot;&gt;&lt;a&gt;2.11    Nomenclature&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following acronyms and abbreviations are used throughout this document and are defined here for convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;wp-block-table&quot;&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      Ltr
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      Liter
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;sup&gt;o&lt;/sup&gt;C
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      Degree Celsius
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;sup&gt;o&lt;/sup&gt;F
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      Fahrenheit
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;3-discussion&quot;&gt;&lt;a&gt;3.    Discussion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have covered the problem and its background in sufficient depth and breadth in the Analysis section. Please refer to section 2 or Design Study Summary for more information about problem and its context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will see some more insights into the process we followed from planning to data collection to how we arrived at the solutions. We will also go through how we captured the data and observed the users. We will discuss in details the mock ups for the recommendations that we have proposed and some alternative ways of doing those recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are also going to evaluate our assumptions and their effects on our recommendations and mock ups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will also evaluate our mock ups for their pros and cons. Let’s us first star with the observation methods we decided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;31-pre-observation-planning&quot;&gt;3.1    Pre observation planning&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We identified the key contacts that we will be communicating with and at what specified time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pondered our attention on who are our users and stake holder and jolted down few goals for the user samples. We planned well what will be the size of our samples and that we will pick some users from each of the following samples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Age wise (Children, Young, Old)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gender wise (Male, Female)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Culture (City, Village)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Location wise (Hot, Cold, Rainy, Desert)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;32-observational-methods&quot;&gt;3.2    Observational Methods&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We focused more on contextual observation because it provides you the context and working condition of the user in its environment and then you can make yourself aware of the workflow he is following and how he is interacting with the refrigerator. By getting this information, you can better observe the user and can find inefficiencies (opportunity areas) in the workflow or usage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We received lots of data regarding the modularity when we were seeing the participants performing their tasks and not using particular areas for a long time, we interjected on the spot questions that why it is happening, that gave us more insight for data collection at lower level details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had to struggle a bit for getting surveys because people were avoiding them. But after we convinced them that it is totally anonymous and no personal information will be recorded, we got few key inputs from survey participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;33-assumptions&quot;&gt;3.3    Assumptions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sample Size:&lt;/strong&gt; Our Sample size is around 20-25, we have included people ranging from villages to cities, from young to old generation, both genders, novice (villager) and experts (mechanic), persons from different profession. Though the sample set is small but it is diverse and we got similar kind of responses from similar user profiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; If this assumption of diversity and reasonable sample size is not met then the data outcome can be biased in one or two areas, which can affect the recommendations we will give and it can be deviated from the voice of most of the customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anonymous Surveys:&lt;/strong&gt; We conducted survey anonymously, just asked them what kind of user they are. We didn’t need any personal data to seek what is the voice of our customers. These kinds of surveys work when people want to participate and contribute ideas but don’t want to come outside in front seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; If this assumption is not met, then user may feel tracked with their personal information and psychologically they may not feel comfortable and may not give their full capacity data due to the mentioned reasons. If this happen, we can only get very few samples and those can’t be treated valuable as the participation is not free to think and act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refrigerator Environment:&lt;/strong&gt; We have limited our scope with only the interaction and usage with the refrigerator. We have done very less research on the environment and workflow around the refrigerator. We have analyzed that these kind of special conditions and environment use cases are few ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if this assumption is not met, we may observe some voids in the data related to environment and workflows. Though we have captured some environments like Canteen Kitchen, Home kitchens, but the study was not extensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;34-debriefing&quot;&gt;3.4    Debriefing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During debrief we assembled at a place of choice and time that we already agreed upon in planning. This session started with every one writing their key findings on the different color notes and posting it on the white board. It was a very interactive session, where each person was talking about some of the interesting things he found during the observation, while posting the notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with our key findings in terms of user needs, we also captured some environment of refrigerator usage so that we can brainstorm on design part during brainstorming session. Some user environments were placed on the board; refer to the column 1 of notes in Figure 1 for more details. Figure 2 and 3 are also part of debriefing sessions; you can refer them for more insights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;35-recommendations&quot;&gt;3.5    Recommendations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the debrief session, on the same day, we collated the data and prioritized it to focus on the important findings of the user research. After all the arguments and counter arguments by each team member, we jolted down the key recommendations. But before we discuss the recommendations, I would like to walk you through what user were saying about the findings during interviews, surveys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please refer to Figure 12 for the visual representation of user responses for each category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-8.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1139&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 8 – User responses per category&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the Figure 12, it is evident that most users want to see:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More functionality in their refrigerator, modular design, they want everything fast and automated about their refrigerator.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some kind of visual or sound indication of refrigerator functioning and running status.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Exterior is also on users’ priority list because they want to see and control everything about the refrigerator without the door every time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Users were also having problems with mobility to easily move and clean the refrigerator.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Users also wanted some solutions to cope with odor (rotten food items, taste).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;36-mockups-and-prototyping&quot;&gt;3.6    Mockups and Prototyping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got the top recommendations as discussed in section 3.5. I am going to explain in depth the solutions brainstormed and generated with mockups and drawings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modular Design&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For making refrigerator more modular and adaptable is to make adjustable horizontal and vertical dividers so you can get the flexible space for variety of containers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with this, provision of modular freezer and vegetables sections can be provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freezer can be pulled out from the top and can be placed at the bottom and veg section can be placed on the top based on the season (winter or summer) or as per the usage patterns. There can be a provision of some button in/control outside the freezer section to convert it into veg section and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provision of dividing the main door into numbers of smaller doors can be provided, so to reach to a particular section of the refrigerator, you need not to open the complete big door. Figure 9 explains the points visually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-9.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1140&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 9 – Mock up for Modular Design&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transparent Doors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By providing the transparent doors and side walls for the home use can greatly increase the ease of use and satisfaction of the buyers because they need not to open the refrigerator every time just to check if something is placed inside; they can check the things from outside to better plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This concept is being used in super markets but not penetrated homes yet. Although solution may not sound aesthetic as it exposes all your things placed in the refrigerator to the outsiders in your home. The solution for that can be providing some control outside to change the transparency of door back to opaque and vice versa. Check the Figure below to get the feel how it will look if implemented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-11.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1142&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 10 – Mock up for Transparent Doors and sides&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital display, mobility, help and labels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 11 explains all these needs. Wheels are provided for better mobility. Wheels can be provided with the locks to fix the wheels in one place and stopping them from unintentional motion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For better controlling refrigerator and knowing its status, some kind of digital LCD/LED display can be provided outside the door. That will make the tasks easy of controlling temperature (with options of &lt;sup&gt;o&lt;/sup&gt;C or &lt;sup&gt;o&lt;/sup&gt;F), humidity from outside without opening the refrigerator. Along with the controls, this display will also show the information about refrigerator like its capacity (e.g. 200 Ltr), current temperature inside refrigerator, odor level or other kind of visual warnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternate approach for the “outside display” can be a remote control with inbuilt display. This remote can control the refrigerator settings and shows its different properties like current temperature, humidity, odor level, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;User help can also be displayed on the display for easy accessibility. If a hard copy of the help is to be provided, a help slot can be provided to keep the help book or some other related document at a handy place. Help can include the topics for example best practices of how to use a refrigerator efficiently, what kind of things can be put inside the refrigerator and at what temperature, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-12.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1143&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 11 – Mock up for Display, settings outside, help slot, wheels for mobility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Output ports and light body&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Output ports” is an innovative feature as shown in Figure 12 below. Output port means that we provide some sort of output to external containers to cool their contents. It means you are extending your refrigerator using these output ports through a connecting pipe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with this, disposable fiber glass can be used for building the non-electrical parts of the refrigerator because this material is lighter than traditional material, less brittle, flexible and also doesn’t hurt the environment. This adaptation can ease the movement of the refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image-13.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1144&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure 12 – Mock up for output cooling ports to cool outside containers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;appendix &lt;/a&gt;A – USer roles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;User roles captured during data analysis are given below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RM, PC, etc. are short code words that are mapped to our users and we have adopted this convention to keep their anonymity. Many users of similar requirements are clubbed under appropriate roles and are not shown for brevity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Role: RM the professional (Female, Age: 28 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Working professional and housewife&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Perfectionist&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime uses the refrigerator for keeping food/cold drinks and eatables. Work outside so that much interaction is not there but being&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A professional this person have some good knowledge about the refrigerator. She is aware of the brands leading in the segment. Brand awareness is there but logical decision is made if need to choose another refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User role: PC the City Home User (Female, Age: 28 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;An engineer&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Housewife&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;has teaching experience in instrumentation and control&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a home user, the interaction with the refrigerator is enormous for keeping milk, foods, water, ice, vegetables, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She knows the basics about the refrigerator and its working. Aware of the different brands and like his/her brands very closely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User role: V the villager (Male, Age: 30 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Villager, less educated&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Taxi driver&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a village home user they are comfortable in basic usage. They just need refrigerator to do their basic things like food, water, milk, etc. Not aware of brands much. Cost is important to buy a refrigerator over all other benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User role: GR the Canteen Person (Male, Age: 30 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Office canteen personal&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Less Educated&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a canteen person, they heavily use their refrigerator and know what to put in and how to control its setting easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User role: PT the Village Home User (Female, Age: 60 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a village home user they are comfortable in basic usage. They just need refrigerator to do their basic things like food, water, milk, etc. Not aware of brands much. Cost is important to buy a refrigerator over all other benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User role: AC the Nurse (Female, Age: 25 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nurse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a nurse and doctor profession, she has the basic knowledge to use it and clean it. She is well educated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Role: HR the Mechanic (Male, Age: 35 Years)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A good mechanic to repair all kind of refrigerators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mechanic understands all the aspects of a refrigerator and is well educated/trained to repair/use the refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;appendix B – Problem Areas captured by observation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem and stories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the round brackets, we have given code names of some of the users that we interviewed. The list is comprehensive and not full to maintain the clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1&lt;strong&gt;. Customization and functional changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(JK) should have compartments like fruit sections, vegetable, eggs water&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) 2-door freezer on bottom&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(SLN) Push button to change from FREEZER to NORMAL refrigerator mode&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(VM) REFRIGERATOR can be used as one container&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(ST) Separator day wise section for milk bags and other milk products&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Single door 2-way opening option along with separate electric connector at both ends&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(ST) Fruit, vegetables should have separator door and should be boxed below milk container and this assembly should be at center of the refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(ST) Glass and foldable tray should be made available, foldable tray will act as divider between two perishable items&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) Compartments can be customized and tailored as per demand&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Texting\Mailing to cellphone facility and handle for cellphone wireless phone&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(R) Cosmetics\Non-perishable items stored separately in compartments&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(R) Separate section for medicines which can viewed from outside (transparent)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(SM) instead of vertical heighted refrigerator, horizontal refrigerator model can be used in homes to get more visibility of the items.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                It can take more space horizontally which is scarce in big cities. This model can be helpful in smaller cities and villages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Label\help&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(JK) proper labeling of compartments, sections, area and controlling inputs&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Help guide on the refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Maintenance guide for cleaning, power cuts on refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Exterior changes\improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) Make some compartment Transparent to minimize frequent open\close of refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) Backside protection where compressor and circuits are located&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Integrated FM radio\music system as part of refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Having OVEN as an extensible assembly and optional with refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Cool air blower to inject cool air in items to cool them&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PC) Temperature control knob outside of refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(ST) Non-veg storage compartment having sections&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(JK) Strong but sleek exterior&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) Finger print enabled Touch based lock&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PC) Push button locks instead of mechanical lock&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4&lt;strong&gt;. Interior changes\improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(JK) Suitable lightening for each compartment&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) Tray should be aligned properly and should function smoothly&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) 2-door freezer at the bottom&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(AN) Gap between wires of the tray cause imbalance&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PT) Need different design for different capacity of bottle&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PT) Side tray is difficult to remove and clean&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(AN) Customizable Covering of bottle section&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Inputs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(JK) Replace switched by touch inputs&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Mobile application to register number of FMCG products in refrigerator and connecting it the Internet&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(SM) In case of refrigerator full of capacity, need ports to cool items externally&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Efficient power consumption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) Cooling reduces as soon as power cuts off&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PC) Reduce power consumption&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(R) Auto Defrost facility in refrigerator&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PC) Reduce danger of electrocution&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(V) Inbuilt invertor&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(JK) indicators for temperature, total capacity and available capacity so that i need not open the doors every time.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(PC) Temperature control arrow is confusing, sometime i found it which direction to Increase and which to decrease.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(SLN) Digital display outside&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Door&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) refrigerator should have different doors for different compartment instead of main door.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) door closing should be slow as it is noisy and unbalancing the things placed inside.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(AN) when pushing doors, things get imbalanced.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) there is not alarm when door remains open, should be a provision of alarming.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(AN) can’t open door if it is near the wall, some way should be there to get the things out.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Mobility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) Wheels to move refrigerator so that while cleaning the floor and cleaning the refrigerator i can move it easily.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) Refrigerator should be mobile but should be steady when not moving.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) Separate take way box that i can put and take when going outside.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(MT) height adjustable wheel base.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. Odor handling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(RM) separate compartment for the items having odors.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) Detection of rotten items.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) automatic indication for bad odor such as beep.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) Smell of one item should not be mixed with other items. I have encountered this problem many times where one food smell is coming from other eatable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;(CM) Food taste doesn’t seem fresh; it is like we are eating some stale food.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;Appendix C – &lt;/a&gt;Survey Results (UNprocessed)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problems or improvements in usage or design during the use of refrigerator faced by you can be shared. Please provide the reason also for your improvement areas in the refrigerator design and functionality.&lt;br /&gt;
For examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Section of vegetables should be spacious to put more vegetables.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Refrigerator door handle is not at a right place.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Power consumption is high.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should be fungus proof because i have seen black fungus type inside refrigerator and it may spoil food.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Complete list of all responses given to this question&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Temperature controller panel is deep inside the refrigerator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No light in Ice Cooling part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cooling should change as changes in weather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; It remains fixed irrespective of outside temperature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Door side cooling should be good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freezer is not working properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulator is not working properly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Auto temperature control according to weather should be provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Different temperature control for different climate should be there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need wheels which will help to relocate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need indication if refrigerator going in bad state e.g., status of compressor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem faces by user while keeping Birthday cakes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem faces by user keeping the 1.5 liter cold drink bottles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doors slides down due to weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some types of refrigerator make much noise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Old refrigerators are not disposed-off in correct way. These contain some hazardous gases and materials that should be disposed correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There should be separate temperature control for normal section and freezer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some types of refrigerators, back panel becomes very hot which is not good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refrigerators should work\keep inside goods in better condition even when power supply is cut off. This will help in the areas\cities where there is frequent power cutoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refrigerator should be portable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should have moving wheels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tray for collecting water should be big enough- If there are different doors for separate compartments, these doors should be see through, transparent so that i know which stuff is where.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back design is not that good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Improvement: Remote Control that can open the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not good use of space inside it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not much resistant to electrical fluctuations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Door should be transparent to see the things without opening the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;Appendix D – Recommendations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the proposed solutions are given below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                &lt;strong&gt;1 &amp;amp; 2 Functionality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. This is the problem, we have never seen a single refrigerator labeling all the important parts or connections or circuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                2. Help guide for how to use a refrigerator and its best practices of setting temperature and putting things inside and how, it can be put in a side slot in the refrigerator that can be easily accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                3. If refrigerator has good large display outside, help guide can be also be provided electronically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remote control to open the door or control the temperature or other settings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Exterior changes\improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. Transparent doors and walls check the diagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Can be easily provided but we need to see the aesthetic effects after that. If we can also provide some way/button         to switch between transparent and opaque walls, then it can be a great ease of use and interaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Otherwise, we can have camera installed internally that can display the inside story outside on display.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Interior changes\improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. Modular design, check the diagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Inputs/outputs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Refrigerator can be provided with ports (like an usb ports) where you can connect compatible pipes to cool container outside the refrigerator. This can extend the refrigerator capacity. But there can be some limitation like to prevent leaking pipes or containers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Some mechanism should be present there to detect these kinds of leaks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                It is looking promising but we need to observe the ROI on its research by conducting more exhaustive surveys and VOCs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Efficient power consumption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. We can improve in energy use by leveraging the current research of inverter technology&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                2. If refrigerator is empty then it should be auto switched off or reduce the energy consumption if the cooling is needed only       in specific part or compartment inside the refrigerator. Can be done easily by using sensors firing after a certain interval    frequency to check the refrigerator is empty or not.               &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                3. For the display or light inside we can use,  high efficient LEDs, LEDs consume power of 1/10 of the bulb used inside the    refrigerator and provide better light output with less heat dissipation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                4. Electric fluctuation can be avoided by built in stabilizers, many makers have model that have this feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. Can be easily implemented, refer the diagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Door&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. Door should be slowed down when it is pushed hard either by mistake or by a child, so not to imbalance the things,                liquids placed inside it. It can be easily done using the latest motion suppression and vibration reduction technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Mobility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Mobility can easily be done with balancing and sturdy wheels that can handle some vibration due to the compressor and motor      running. Locks can be provided to wheels to lock their motion once the refrigerator is installed in the environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Customers prefer the brand mobility solution as they believe them to be of equal quality as the refrigerator is. They don’t want to      go to the local vendor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. Odor handling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Odor can be handled by placing a sensor detecting some gases that are released from the rotten things. Beep warning can be provided to the user along with flashing visual signal on outer refrigerator display. Electronic nose that detects like        nose gases like sulphide, ammonia, carbon monoxide, etc. can be used to detect odor and integrated with microcontroller logic   to send signals for warning (visually and sound).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Food taste can be improved with the air flow regulation/restriction inside the refrigerator. Suggesting the customer best practices         to avoid this situation is a good viable option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                Best Practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                1. Always put a lid on your containers with food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                2. If some vegetable/fruit/meat is cut, please wrap in a thin plastic or put in a special container inside the refrigerator for       that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;                3. We can control the temperature inside the refrigerator doesn’t rises too fast or too slow so that                 you can get your expected temperature setting whenever you want food. This can easily be achieved by improving the design           of the compressor to achieve high cooling velocity. Speed up the cooling gas liquidation and vaporization using the latest.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="research" /><category term="Startups" /><category term="research" /><summary type="html">Subject 1.&amp;nbsp; Problem/Purpose Increase satisfaction and ease of use when interacting with a refrigerator. Basically, we need to improve the design and functionalities of the refrigerator to make it more user-friendly, easy to use and feature rich to satisfy our customers. To achieve this goal, we have to hear what our customers and stakeholders are looking for in a good solution. 2.&amp;nbsp; References International Journal of Refrigeration Principles of refrigeration working Washington University at St Louis http://panasonic.com/industrial/includes/pdf/invertercompressors-improvingefficiency.pdfhttp://freeonlinesurveys.com/rendersurvey.asp?sid=so68kif9b3jo0ad958434 &amp;nbsp; 3.&amp;nbsp; Assumptions Surveys conducted are anonymous, only type of user (home, working, etc.) is askedOur scope is limited to the interaction with the refrigerator; very less or no consideration is given to the environment in which refrigerator is being used.Survey and Interview sample size is 20-25 peoples having different level of interactions and use cases with the refrigerator. We assumed this sample size is enough for our scope.We are assuming that we are doing all these exercises to improve a business position in the market. &amp;nbsp; 4.&amp;nbsp; Results The main pain areas resulting from user interviews, contextual observations, surveys &amp;nbsp;with the refrigerator use are: The refrigerator is not modular and doesn’t suit the containers if they are very large or small.Very painful to every time open the door just to see what is there inside and control the temperature.Very difficult to move from one place to other to clean it or floor under it.Almost all the participants wanted some indication in a display like temperature, capacity, odor level etc. The other interesting finding is that customers like their brands with their heart and would not like to switch to different brand if purchasing a new refrigerator but can reconsider their decision if reliability in the form of warranty is provided. 5.&amp;nbsp; Conclusions The main findings are that user (voice of almost all users) wants to save the time while interacting with and using the refrigerator. He wants nearly everything to be automated, handy, and easy to use with low learning curve. We have suggested few design changes and inclusion of new technologies like electronic nose to detect odor in the refrigerator and alarming, use of LEDs for saving power and providing uniform lighting, inverter technology of using the compressor heat to efficiently convert back to electric power and demand based power usage. Proposed Recommendations: Provision of giving settings controls and LCD/LED display outside the refrigerator so the user needs not to open the door and bend every time just to check or change the temperature, see inside the refrigerator.Transparent Walls with reversible opaque capability. Person with the press of switch or remote can switch between transparent exterior and opaque exterior.Modular design &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Innovative Thinking</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/23/innovative-thinking/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Innovative Thinking" /><published>2019-02-23T13:26:33+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-23T13:26:33+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/23/innovative-thinking</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/23/innovative-thinking/">&lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_19 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins doubleReplace replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;19&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;19&quot;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/g&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for this article – &lt;strong&gt;Roberta B. Ness (worked on Ovarian Cancer)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though in today’s world we are more eager to invent and do more but innovation in healthcare and many other sectors like water treatment, garbage cleaning etc. is very slow for example there is no cheap cancer treatment, &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_105 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;105&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;105&quot;&gt;cost-effectiveness&lt;/g&gt; of other medical treatments, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frames define our thinking, the kind of expectations in a particular situation. Frames are cognitive and emotions expectations and can also result in reactions. For example – you are expecting a hello from a person meeting you the first time, instead, he tells you who are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This breaks the flow or assumptions in your thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frame&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:left&quot;&gt;
  To innovate &amp;#8211; we must break frames. Scientists used to assume that bacteria can’t grow in acidic environment of the stomach, break this assumptions and check the data to explain anomalies.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be an innovator – you must be a great observer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flipping the view&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God creates every creature to perfection, Darwin flipped it and said it is not &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_29 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling&quot; id=&quot;29&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;29&quot;&gt;perfection&lt;/g&gt; and &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_40 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;40&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;40&quot;&gt;lets&lt;/g&gt; find the reason for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darwin imagined himself as plant to understand the evolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analogy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the cause, cells that are around ovarian are same as in breathing pipe (airway&lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_10 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_disable\_anim_appear Punctuation multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;10&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;10&quot;&gt;).&lt;/g&gt; Is there can be &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_31 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins doubleReplace replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;31&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;31&quot;&gt;reason&lt;/g&gt; that smoking can also affect ovary like our airways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Élie Metchnikoff&lt;/strong&gt; – the discovery of white blood cell (tried suicide 2 times, believed in Darwin theory). He did put a thorn in a fish and found white blood cells around it to protect from the attack. Read about this great scientist to know of his thinking approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be bold not cautious.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;World need innovation rather than invention for the sake of patent filing. We need to improve the world and solve problems rather than settle in life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="Career" /><category term="Life" /><category term="Motivation" /><category term="research" /><category term="innovation" /><category term="thinking" /><summary type="html">Inspiration for this article – Roberta B. Ness (worked on Ovarian Cancer)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Microservices Part 1 – Basic Concepts</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/17/microservices-part-1-basic-concepts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Microservices Part 1 – Basic Concepts" /><published>2019-02-17T13:50:22+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-17T13:50:22+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/17/microservices-part-1-basic-concepts</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/17/microservices-part-1-basic-concepts/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-microservice-is-an-architectural-style-with-small-services-which-are&quot;&gt;A microservice is an architectural style with small services which are&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;isolated,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;loosely-coupled&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;works on a single concern.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Own their own data&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lightweight communication usually with HTTP Restful API&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Built around business capabilities/domain, example below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DDD (&lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_13 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;13&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;13&quot;&gt;Domain driven&lt;/g&gt; design) is the way to go while &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_25 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;25&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;25&quot;&gt;designig&lt;/g&gt; microservices.&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://lh5.googleusercontent.com/OlYKfFDflU8_Pjv-ppbq6CtTeV8-J7O-a6PKceZJSLQWaVU4x30Kf63oKlwyaxHonk01lwI5dR8yqSSZvHd8py7PPTlhhoQGTtP94oPNIEOzeCHnB8LSxuSZcqG2sm-OCgVmWZw-&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Independently deployable by automated means&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Right tech for right problem – each microservice can be implemented on its own tech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advantages&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Language independent as conform to HTTP Restful&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Individual team for each microservice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scalable&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fault tolerance&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Container friendly (docker, kubernete)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fast iteration for adding code&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;small development teams,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;shorter development cycles&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;flexibility in language selection&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;enhanced service scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disadvantages&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complex interactions – System + Operational&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Overhead of communication across databases and servers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Resource and nw overhead&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complex authentication and authorization scheme in the Microservices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design Considerations&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-cutting&lt;/strong&gt;: microservices need not deal with details regarding problems outside their specific scope.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data sharing&lt;/strong&gt; is hard. Microservices tend to favor per-service or per-group databases that can be updated directly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Availability&lt;/strong&gt;: Microservices, by virtue of being isolated and independent, need to be monitored to detect failures.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evolution&lt;/strong&gt;: Microservices tend to evolve fast. Old versions are usually available as long as there are clients who need to consume data from them. Newer versions are exposed in an application-specific way. For instance, with an HTTP/REST API, the version of the microservice may be part of a custom header, or be embedded in the returned data. Account for this.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated deployment&lt;/strong&gt;: The whole reason that microservices are so convenient nowadays is that it is so easy to deploy a new service from a completely clean environment.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interdependencies&lt;/strong&gt;: Keep them to a minimum.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transport and data format&lt;/strong&gt;: Microservices are fit for any transport and data format; however, they are usually exposed publicly through a RESTful API over HTTP. Any data format fit for your information works. HTTP + JSON is very popular these days, but there is nothing stopping you from using protocol-buffers over AMQP, for instance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;microservices are developed almost in isolation. &lt;strong&gt;Cross-cutting concerns&lt;/strong&gt; are dealt with by &lt;strong&gt;upper layers&lt;/strong&gt; in the software stack&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="Startups" /><category term="technology" /><category term="domain driven design" /><category term="microservices" /><category term="Software Architecture" /><summary type="html">A microservice is an architectural style with small services which are</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Annual tax filing for LLP in India</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/17/annual-tax-filing-for-llp-in-india/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Annual tax filing for LLP in India" /><published>2019-02-17T13:41:09+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-17T13:41:09+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/17/annual-tax-filing-for-llp-in-india</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/17/annual-tax-filing-for-llp-in-india/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;llp-stakeholders&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLP Stakeholders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your LLP – you&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MCA – for yearly compliance&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Income Tax Dept – for income tax&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;State govt – professional tax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t wait for the last date, when you have all the data, fill the form asasp and submit it. Near the last date, things happen very fast, your CA might be very busy and you have to pay penalty if your CA takes more time. There is a chance of website going down or be under heavy load which can delay your filings and may results in penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;wp-block-table&quot;&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Forms to be filed&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Last date for filing&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      Annual Return (Form 11)
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      30-05-2017
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      Accounts (Form 8)
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      30-10-2017
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;INCOME TAX RETURN&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Last date for filing&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      In case Audit is not required
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      31-07-2017
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      In Case Audit is required&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      30-09-2017&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      MCA DIY forms directors
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      31-07-2018
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;statutory-compliance-after-incorporation-of-the-llp&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Statutory Compliance after Incorporation of the LLP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_33 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;33&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;33&quot;&gt;formation&lt;/g&gt; of Limited Liability Partnership, every LLP firm shall be required to comply with following statutory requirements as per LLP act 2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-maintain-financial-and-file-accounts&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A. Maintain financial and file accounts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a&lt;/strong&gt;) To maintain proper books of accounts relating to its affairs for each year on cash or accrual basis and according to the double entry system of accounting and shall maintain the same at the registered office of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;b&lt;/strong&gt;) The accounts of LLP shall be audited by an auditor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;b-returns-and-records-required-by-llp&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B. Returns and records required by LLP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;wp-block-table&quot;&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Books of Account&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;LLP should maintain proper books of account.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Minute Book&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Minute book should be maintained to record minutes of meetings of partners and managing/executive &amp;nbsp;committee of partners.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Change in partners&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Any change in partner and designated partner (admission, resignation, cessation, death, expulsion) should be filed electronically in e-form 4 within 30 days of change with fees.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Supplementary LLP agreement&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Such admission and cessation will alter mutual rights and duties of partner shall change. Hence, supplementary LLP agreement will be required which is also required to be filed in e-form 3 within 30 days of change with fees&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Statement of Account and solvency&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Statement of Account and Solvency (SAS) is to be filed annually in e-form 8 with required fees. It is to be filed within 30 days from expiry of 6 months from end of each financial year i.e. by 30th October.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Annual Return&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Annual Return should be filed with ROC in e-form 11 with filing fees, within 60 days from close of financial year i.e. by 30th&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;sup&gt; &lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Heavy penalty&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Heavy penalty of Rs 100 per day for late filing of returns.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Inspection of documents&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      Incorporation document (form 2), Annual Return (form 11), Statement of Account and Solvency (SAS) (form 8 ) and Name of partners and changes, if any, made therein (form 4) are available for public inspection on payment of fees but  LLP agreement is not available for public inspection].
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;c-compliance-of-meetings-of-llp-as-per-llp-agreement&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C. Compliance of Meetings of LLP as per LLP agreement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table class=&quot;wp-block-table&quot;&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Sr. No.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Nature of Meeting&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Number of meetings&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Period&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;First General Meeting&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;N.A.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Within 30 days of incorporation&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;General Meeting&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;In 1 Financial Year&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;Executive Committee&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
    &lt;td&gt;
      &lt;strong&gt;In 1 Financial Year&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MCA – Form 8 and 11&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Form 8 ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the declaration given by all Designated Partners of LLP that whether they are able &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_5 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Style replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;5&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;5&quot;&gt;to&lt;/g&gt; pay its debts in full as they become due in the normal course of business or not. LLP firm shall be required to prepare Statement of Accounts and Solvency which shall be filed by all designated partners within 30 days along with prescribed fees, from the end of six months of the financial year to which statement of accounts relate with Registrar of Companies (RoC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contents of Form 8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part A&lt;/strong&gt; – Statement of Solvency&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part B&lt;/strong&gt; – Statement of Accounts, Statement of Income and Expenditure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attachments&lt;/strong&gt; – Disclosure under Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises Development Act, 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Form 8 is to be by signed digitally by two Designated partners and certified by Chartered Accountant(in Whole-time practice)/ Company Secretary (in &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_4 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;4&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;4&quot;&gt;Whole time&lt;/g&gt; practice) Cost Accountant (in Whole-time practice).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Section 34 of Limited Liability Act, 2008 read with LLP rules, every LLP shall file Statement of Accounts and solvency under e-form 8 with prescribed fee within a period of thirty days from the end of six months of the financial year to which such statement relates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Form 11 ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Form 11 is Annual Return containing number of partners, total contribution received by all partners, details of partners, details of body corporate as partners, summary of partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every LLP shall file Annual Return within sixty days from the closure of the financial year along with prescribed fees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due date of filing Form 11 is 30th May for each year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note If LLP fails to file Form-11 within &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_4 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins doubleReplace replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;4&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;4&quot;&gt;prescribed&lt;/g&gt; time, the designated partners shall be liable to be punishable with fine which shall not be less than Rs. 25000 but which may extend to five lakh rupees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Income Tax Dept – income tax returns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ITR 5 , you can use cleartax online platform to file your taxes easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need GST if turn over is above 20 lakh per annum (as of date 17/Feb/2019). Apply on &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_20 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;20&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;20&quot;&gt;gst&lt;/g&gt; govt website, it is easy and you don’t need any dependency on anybody if you are a startup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Tax (PT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to pay PT tax to the state govt. if you pay salary to employees. Just check the rules. you need to request a professional tax enrollment certificate from your tax commissioner.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="Startups" /><category term="gst" /><category term="startup" /><category term="tax" /><summary type="html">LLP Stakeholders</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Few thoughts on Origin of Universe</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/16/few-thoughts-on-origin-of-universe/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Few thoughts on Origin of Universe" /><published>2019-02-16T22:12:36+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-16T22:12:36+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/16/few-thoughts-on-origin-of-universe</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/16/few-thoughts-on-origin-of-universe/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big bang&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before big bang – &lt;strong&gt;Inflation&lt;/strong&gt; (more or less dense universe) might have happened. Universe had violet expansion before hot big bang&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theory of multiple universe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on the trend of multiple stars, multiple galaxy, scientists think that Big bang keep happening always. Different universe have different physical laws&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is difference in 4 forces strengths on earth life may not exist, it is a merely coincidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theory of one universe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our universe expand and then contracts to create a big bang again, this theory is called the T&lt;strong&gt;heory of Eternal Universe.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fate of the universe – how it will end&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second law of thermodynamics, with time things gets more disordered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Birth of Stars&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First stars started shining after 100 Million years of Big Bang. But Sun was born after 9 Billions year of Big Bang. 1.1 Billions years from 2018, it will become 10% brighter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 Billions years from 2018 it will be 4X brighter and ocean will be no more&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Star formation rate has slowed down to half from 10billions year to today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Sun will become red giant which will engulf the mercury and earth all and then collapse in to a dense mass which will never create a star and will lock the matter forever&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Black holes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In milky way lies a super massive black hole 4 Millions X sun mass. 2 to 3 X mass of sun, stars become black hole&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theory of big rip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When space starts expanding, keep expanding. Dark energy keep becoming strong and keep tearing matter apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflationary multiverse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though our universe dies but new universes keep coming. Our research can become like religion books in far future world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People will not be able to reproduce what is written in scientific books or papers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GW170817, first documented collision of two neutron stars using LIGO&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;wp-block-embed__wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data visualization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.openspaceproject.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.openspaceproject.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://virdir.ncsa.illinois.edu/partiview/&quot;&gt;http://virdir.ncsa.illinois.edu/partiview/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/marksubbarao/Uniview&quot;&gt;http://github.com/marksubbarao/Uniview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citizen science astro proj&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.zooniverse.org/projects/marckuchner/backyard-worlds-planet-9&quot;&gt;http://www.zooniverse.org/projects/marckuchner/backyard-worlds-planet-9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="space" /><category term="big bang" /><category term="inflation" /><category term="space" /><summary type="html">Big bang</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Airbnb Data Science team experience – Jeff Feng</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/15/airbnb-data-science-team-experience-jeff-feng/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Airbnb Data Science team experience – Jeff Feng" /><published>2019-02-15T23:53:39+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-15T23:53:39+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/15/airbnb-data-science-team-experience-jeff-feng</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/15/airbnb-data-science-team-experience-jeff-feng/">&lt;p&gt;Without experimentation, if we release a new feature and see the following graph, we can infer that with the introduction of a new feature the sales have increased. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-6.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1071&quot; width=&quot;428&quot; height=&quot;245&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if we could have done experiments, we may found that it is not true. In the absence of this new feature, the sales might have increased drastically, the reason for this can be anything. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-10.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1075&quot; width=&quot;411&quot; height=&quot;241&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Controlled experiments are building block for decision making &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How useful is this feature &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it moving towards my and company goal &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How team is performing &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Characteristics about experimentation at Airbnb – different in different companies &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-8-1024x458.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1073&quot; width=&quot;450&quot; height=&quot;201&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data related tools and Infra &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They use tableau and superset extensively &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-9-1024x383.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1074&quot; width=&quot;438&quot; height=&quot;163&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt; &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-7.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1072&quot; width=&quot;284&quot; height=&quot;144&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to make sense of this data &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  Apache Superset &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can analyze billions of rows in no time. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-11-1024x506.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1076&quot; width=&quot;414&quot; height=&quot;204&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt; &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-12-1024x349.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1077&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Portal&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Airbnb has a data portal for all the data related work different teams/individual have done. They use the similar tech to google page rank, its kind of search engine. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-13-1024x512.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1078&quot; width=&quot;568&quot; height=&quot;284&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data Education &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data is at the core of everything. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-14-1024x531.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1079&quot; width=&quot;347&quot; height=&quot;179&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt; &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-15-1024x437.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1080&quot; width=&quot;381&quot; height=&quot;162&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ML is everywhere in Airbnb. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-16-1024x491.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1081&quot; width=&quot;361&quot; height=&quot;173&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ML mapped to the every step of the process flow  &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-17-1024x549.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1082&quot; width=&quot;371&quot; height=&quot;198&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="research" /><category term="technology" /><category term="airbnb" /><category term="machine learning" /><summary type="html">Without experimentation, if we release a new feature and see the following graph, we can infer that with the introduction of a new feature the sales have increased. </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Model-Based Machine Learning</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/15/model-based-learning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Model-Based Machine Learning" /><published>2019-02-15T23:37:44+05:30</published><updated>2019-02-15T23:37:44+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/15/model-based-learning</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/15/model-based-learning/">&lt;p&gt;ML not equal to data + black box &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ML = data + assumptions  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Lunch Theorem&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per free lunch theorem, without assumptions we can’t build anything. We can’t have one generic &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_4 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace&quot; id=&quot;4&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;4&quot;&gt;algo&lt;/g&gt; that is applicable for all the problems.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have &lt;strong&gt;constraints &lt;/strong&gt;like  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  assumptions,  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  prior knowledge,  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  domain knowledge &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; when dealing with problems and without considering these how we can solve a problem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data + prior knowledge&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Detection of a person in frame &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a simple approach, we will need many images with person at different location. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But with this knowledge, we can develop transformations to shift a person in the image and then train the model on these images instead of acquiring those images. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We tend to think about Big data that we can develop weak models and can forget the constraints/assumptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 2 types of sizes &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  1. computation size &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  2. statistical size &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&quot;alignleft is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1060&quot; width=&quot;243&quot; height=&quot;198&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;

&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1061&quot; width=&quot;236&quot; height=&quot;195&quot; /&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computationally small but statistical big &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without assumptions, how we can predict a current value for a new voltage value?  On the right side, we can take into consideration about V = IR and can be confident that the line is good predictor for future voltage values. This dataset is small in computational size but big in statistical size. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1063&quot; width=&quot;384&quot; height=&quot;261&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Statistically small but computationally big &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above data is computationally big, take a simple example of a &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_5 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins doubleReplace replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;5&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;5&quot;&gt;black&lt;/g&gt; and white image of 10X10 pixel, all the combinations can yield combinations that might be more than the total number of atoms in the universe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless we make assumptions, it is very difficult to do computation with these big set of images. This above images data can be computationally very large but statistically very small. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model based ML&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of getting lost in the sea of algorithms/models/research papers, we should use model-based learning to use data and assumptions to derive ML algorithm. We should work mainly on defining our assumptions about the problem very clearly.  &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;wp-block-embed__wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Translate your assumptions into a model and that is the core of model-based learning. If our assumptions are sound/strong then we get much more information from the same amount of data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can we develop a tool to do it automatically? Can this dream be true? &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-4.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1064&quot; width=&quot;288&quot; height=&quot;235&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User &amp;amp; Movies&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Predict the question marks – whether a user like or dislike those movie for which he has not given a answer. 10ks of movies, 10Ms of users. &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1062&quot; width=&quot;433&quot; height=&quot;331&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt; &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image is-resized&quot;&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-5-1024x507.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1065&quot; width=&quot;618&quot; height=&quot;306&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on my like or dislike, ML is suggesting movies closer to green area that I can like for sure and closer to red area for movies that I may not like. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is learning my behavior and suggesting me titles based on the populations similar to me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Information (as per information theory by Shanon) is the surprise from data. Just like above movie ML algo suggest me movies closer to green area and I pick then there is a very less surprise in the data and suggestions don’t move big. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But instead of liking the movie, if I dislike it, it is a big surprise for the algo and movies suggestions move big. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quantifying uncertainty&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uncertainty is an essential part of machine learning and it is a modern view of ML. &lt;strong&gt;Bayes theorem&lt;/strong&gt; is at the core of it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BT: P(A/B) = [P(A) * P(B/A)]/P(B) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bishop view on Healthcare&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;wp-block-embed__wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is one of the biggest opportunities but complex also. Personalized healthcare can be a phenomenon suggesting you personalized course of treatment because as an individual each one of us is unique. It is like machine can learn our movies preferences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; This can happen by analyzing the info from other millions of people.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  Cloud based tech + ML tech + Domain experts (from Hospitals like clinicians, doctors, radiologists, etc.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trust and privacy in the Data&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data is encrypted so it is only accessible to those who have keys but It can become vulnerable while being processed. So Microsoft has taken care of processing data in &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_7 gr-alert gr\_gramm gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim Grammar only-ins replaceWithoutSep&quot; id=&quot;7&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;7&quot;&gt;secure&lt;/g&gt; vault kind of infrastructure where data can be &lt;g class=&quot;gr_ gr\_10 gr-alert gr\_spell gr\_inline\_cards gr\_run\_anim ContextualSpelling&quot; id=&quot;10&quot; data-gr-id=&quot;10&quot;&gt;access&lt;/g&gt; only to people who have keys. It is secure by hardware and software. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Factor Graph&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;wp-block-image&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://sciloo.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/image-18.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;wp-image-1120&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The probability of getting a circular or triangular cookie depends upon which jar we choose. Round circles on the right sides are – one random variable for Jar, one random variable for Cookie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These random variables are driven by their respective probability distribution functions (PDFs) denoted as shaded squares.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>admin@sciloo.com</name></author><category term="research" /><category term="technology" /><category term="healthcare" /><category term="machine learning" /><summary type="html">ML not equal to data + black box </summary></entry></feed>